<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>srcful Blog</title>
        <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog</link>
        <description>srcful Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The first batch - Solaris]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/14/</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/14/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Srcful is excited to announce the latest installations of our energy gateway prototypes. These devices are the backbone of our platform, allowing home owners to connect their solar panels and batteries to the Srcful community and earn tokens for contributing to the energy market.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Srcful is excited to announce the latest installations of our energy gateway prototypes. These devices are the backbone of our platform, allowing home owners to connect their solar panels and batteries to the Srcful community and earn tokens for contributing to the energy market.</p><p>Our energy gateway prototypes are compatible with the most common brands of inverters and batteries in the world. They provide a digital identity to distributed energy resources (DERs), allowing them to transact and prove their energy data on the blockchain. This makes it possible for micro-producers to participate in previously closed ecosystems and monetize their contributions through services like ancillary services.</p><p>The latest installations of our energy gateway prototypes are a significant milestone for our team. We have worked hard to develop a device that is both energy-efficient and secure, with the ability to provide Proof-of-Source and Proof-of-Control. This is the act of proving that the inverters are connected and able to be controlled on demand when delivering flexibility services to the grid. By providing this proof, home owners can earn SRC tokens and contribute to a more sustainable and decentralized energy system.</p><p>The first batch of our energy gateway prototypes, called Solaris, have been installed with inverters from Sungrow, Huawei, and Solaredge. These three brands represent a significant portion of the global market for home inverters, according to a September 2021 report from ResearchAndMarkets. Solaredge had a market share of approximately 38%, followed by Huawei with approximately 23%, and Sungrow with approximately 14%.</p><p>At Srcful, we are committed to revolutionizing the energy market by providing a decentralized community that empowers home owners to participate in the energy market and monetize their contributions. Our energy gateway prototypes are a critical component of our platform, and we are excited to see them in action.</p><p>We are currently working on expanding our installations to new markets and continuing to refine our devices. We are excited to be at the forefront of a new era in energy, and we invite you to join us on this journey.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Join the Srcful Community and Earn Crypto]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/07/</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/07/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Joining the Srcful community is an opportunity to participate in a decentralized energy system that rewards home owners for contributing to the energy market. In this post, we'll provide a step-by-step guide to joining the Srcful community and earning tokens for contributing to the energy market.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joining the Srcful community is an opportunity to participate in a decentralized energy system that rewards home owners for contributing to the energy market. In this post, we'll provide a step-by-step guide to joining the Srcful community and earning tokens for contributing to the energy market.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-1-set-up-a-solana-powered-wallet">Step 1: Set up a Solana-powered wallet<a href="#step-1-set-up-a-solana-powered-wallet" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 1: Set up a Solana-powered wallet" title="Direct link to Step 1: Set up a Solana-powered wallet">​</a></h3><p>To begin participating in the Srcful community, users will need to set up a Solana-powered wallet. This will allow users to interact with the platform, earn tokens through mining, and swap tokens for other tokens or fiat.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-2-connect-solar-panel-or-battery-system">Step 2: Connect solar panel or battery system<a href="#step-2-connect-solar-panel-or-battery-system" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 2: Connect solar panel or battery system" title="Direct link to Step 2: Connect solar panel or battery system">​</a></h3><p>To begin earning SRCT (Srcful token), users will need to connect their own solar panel or battery system using the Srcful Energy Gateway. This device is built on the Sunspec-standard and is compatible with the large brands of inverters on the market. It provides a digital identity to the DER, allowing it to transact and prove its energy data on the blockchain.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-3-monitor-energy-data">Step 3: Monitor energy data<a href="#step-3-monitor-energy-data" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 3: Monitor energy data" title="Direct link to Step 3: Monitor energy data">​</a></h3><p>Users can monitor their energy data and see all of their data on a web platform at <strong><a href="https://explorer.srcful.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://explorer.srcful.io</a></strong>. This will allow them to track their contributions to the decentralized grid and see the tokens they are earning in real-time.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-4-provide-proof-of-source-and-proof-of-control">Step 4: Provide Proof-of-Source and Proof-of-Control<a href="#step-4-provide-proof-of-source-and-proof-of-control" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 4: Provide Proof-of-Source and Proof-of-Control" title="Direct link to Step 4: Provide Proof-of-Source and Proof-of-Control">​</a></h3><p>To earn SRCT, users will need to provide Proof-of-Source, which is the act of proving that their inverters are connected, and Proof-of-Control, which is the ability to be controlled on demand when delivering flexibility services to the grid. All of this can be done through the Srcful Energy Gateway.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-5-swap-tokens-for-other-tokens-or-fiat">Step 5: Swap tokens for other tokens or fiat<a href="#step-5-swap-tokens-for-other-tokens-or-fiat" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 5: Swap tokens for other tokens or fiat" title="Direct link to Step 5: Swap tokens for other tokens or fiat">​</a></h3><p>Users can swap their tokens for other tokens or fiat on available exchanges, allowing them to make extra income.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="step-6-utilize-der-services">Step 6: Utilize DER services<a href="#step-6-utilize-der-services" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Step 6: Utilize DER services" title="Direct link to Step 6: Utilize DER services">​</a></h3><p>Flexibility service providers or energy grids can utilize DER services by buying SRCT. These tokens represent the right to use DER for flexibility services to maintain a stable grid.</p><p>In summary, joining the Srcful community is an opportunity to participate in a decentralized energy system that rewards home owners for contributing to the energy market. By connecting their own solar panels or batteries using the Srcful Energy Gateway, monitoring their energy data, and providing Proof-of-Source and Proof-of-Control, users can earn SRCT and contribute to a more sustainable and decentralized energy system.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Promoting Energy Independence and Resilience through DERs]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/03/</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/02/03/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As the world continues to shift towards a more sustainable energy future, the role of distributed energy resources (DERs) is becoming increasingly important. DERs, like solar panels and batteries, are playing a key role in reducing carbon emissions, increasing energy efficiency, and promoting energy independence. In this post, we'll discuss the benefits of DERs in the context of the energy industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the world continues to shift towards a more sustainable energy future, the role of distributed energy resources (DERs) is becoming increasingly important. DERs, like solar panels and batteries, are playing a key role in reducing carbon emissions, increasing energy efficiency, and promoting energy independence. In this post, we'll discuss the benefits of DERs in the context of the energy industry.</p><p>First and foremost, DERs help to reduce carbon emissions. By generating energy from renewable sources like solar, wind, and hydro, DERs help to reduce the amount of carbon emissions produced by the energy industry. This is critical for addressing the global climate crisis and reducing our reliance on fossil fuels.</p><p>Secondly, DERs can help to increase energy efficiency. By generating energy closer to the point of use, DERs reduce the amount of energy lost during transmission and distribution. This makes the energy system more efficient and reduces the need for expensive upgrades to the energy grid.</p><p>Finally, DERs promote energy independence. By generating energy locally, home owners can become less reliant on the traditional energy system, which is subject to price volatility and power outages. This promotes greater energy security and resilience, and can help to reduce energy costs over the long-term.</p><p>At Srcful, we're committed to promoting the use of DERs by creating a decentralized platform that enables home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. By using DERs, home owners can reduce their carbon footprint, increase their energy efficiency, and promote energy independence.</p><p>In summary, the benefits of DERs are clear. They help to reduce carbon emissions, increase energy efficiency, and promote energy independence. By using DERs and participating in the energy market through platforms like Srcful, home owners can contribute to a more sustainable and decentralized energy system.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secure and Transparent Energy Transactions with Srcful]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/01/16/</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/2023/01/16/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As the lead hardware engineer at Srcful, I'm excited to share with you an overview of our platform's architecture. At Srcful, we're leveraging cutting-edge technologies to create a decentralized platform that enables home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the lead hardware engineer at Srcful, I'm excited to share with you an overview of our platform's architecture. At Srcful, we're leveraging cutting-edge technologies to create a decentralized platform that enables home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.</p><p>One of the key challenges of creating a decentralized platform is ensuring that the devices are up-to-date and secure. To address this challenge, we're using OTA (over-the-air) updates to keep the firmware of the Srcful Energy Gateway up-to-date. These updates are signed by the crypto chip, ensuring that the device is secure and trusted.</p><p>Another challenge is ensuring that the energy data and rewards are transacted securely and transparently on the blockchain. To address this challenge, we've developed a system for signing data packages that are sent to the blockchain. This system ensures that the data is tamper-proof and transparent, which is critical for a decentralized platform.</p><p>Here's an example of how to sign a data package using C++ pseudo code:</p><div class="language-c++ codeBlockContainer_Ckt0 theme-code-block" style="--prism-color:#393A34;--prism-background-color:#f6f8fa"><div class="codeBlockContent_biex"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-c++ codeBlock_bY9V thin-scrollbar"><code class="codeBlockLines_e6Vv"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">void sign_data_package(unsigned char* data, unsigned int len, unsigned char* signature)</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">{</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    // get the private key from the crypto chip</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    unsigned char private_key[32];</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    get_private_key(private_key);</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain" style="display:inline-block"></span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    // calculate the hash of the data</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    unsigned char hash[32];</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    sha256(data, len, hash);</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain" style="display:inline-block"></span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    // sign the hash with the private key</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">    sign(private_key, hash, signature);</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">}</span><br></span></code></pre><div class="buttonGroup__atx"><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" title="Copy" class="clean-btn"><span class="copyButtonIcons_eSgA" aria-hidden="true"><svg class="copyButtonIcon_y97N" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><path d="M19,21H8V7H19M19,5H8A2,2 0 0,0 6,7V21A2,2 0 0,0 8,23H19A2,2 0 0,0 21,21V7A2,2 0 0,0 19,5M16,1H4A2,2 0 0,0 2,3V17H4V3H16V1Z"></path></svg><svg class="copyButtonSuccessIcon_LjdS" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><path d="M21,7L9,19L3.5,13.5L4.91,12.09L9,16.17L19.59,5.59L21,7Z"></path></svg></span></button></div></div></div><p>In addition to these security features, we're also using AI on the edge to prevent gaming of the system. Our platform is designed to prevent users from exploiting the system to earn more rewards than they are entitled to. By using AI on the edge, we're able to detect and prevent fraudulent activities, ensuring that the rewards are distributed fairly and transparently.</p><p>In summary, the architecture of the Srcful platform is designed with security, transparency, and fairness in mind. We're leveraging cutting-edge technologies like OTA updates, crypto chips, and AI on the edge to create a decentralized platform that enables home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. By signing data packages that are sent to the blockchain, we ensure that the data is tamper-proof and transparent, and by using AI on the edge, we prevent fraudulent activities.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earn Crypto with Srcful Energy Gateway]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/earn-crypto-with-srcful-energy-gateway</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/earn-crypto-with-srcful-energy-gateway</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Srcful Energy Gateway is a unique IoT device that plays a critical role in the Srcful platform, enabling home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. It is designed to be compatible with most types of inverters and batteries, making it accessible to a wide range of energy producers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Srcful Energy Gateway is a unique IoT device that plays a critical role in the Srcful platform, enabling home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. It is designed to be compatible with most types of inverters and batteries, making it accessible to a wide range of energy producers.</p><p>The Srcful Energy Gateway is a small device that is installed next to the solar panels or battery system, and it communicates with the Srcful platform to transact energy data and rewards. It provides a digital identity to the distributed energy resource (DER), enabling it to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.</p><p>One of the key benefits of the Srcful Energy Gateway is that it allows home owners to monetize their contributions to the energy market. By earning crypto rewards, home owners can make a return on their investment in renewable energy resources, making it more financially viable for them to adopt these technologies.</p><p>In addition to its compatibility with most types of inverters and batteries, the Srcful Energy Gateway is designed to be highly energy-efficient and built with the highest security standards in mind. We're leveraging several communication methods like wifi, ble, LoRa, and more, to make sure that the device is compatible with the majority of inverters in the world.</p><p>The Srcful Energy Gateway is a unique device that sets us apart from our competitors. While other platforms rely on industrial hardware, we've created a state-of-the-art IoT device that is more energy-efficient and designed to be compatible with most types of inverters and batteries.</p><p>Joining the Srcful community is an opportunity to be part of a growing movement that is changing the energy industry. By participating in the energy market and earning crypto rewards, you'll be contributing to a more sustainable and decentralized grid. And by joining early, you'll have the opportunity to participate in the early stages of the platform and contribute to its growth.</p><p>In summary, the Srcful Energy Gateway is a critical component of the Srcful platform, enabling home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. It is designed to be compatible with most types of inverters and batteries, energy-efficient, and built with the highest security standards in mind. Joining the Srcful community is an opportunity to contribute to a more sustainable and decentralized energy grid, and to make a return on your investment in renewable energy resources.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DERs on blockchain]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/ders-on-blockchain</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/ders-on-blockchain</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Blockchain technology and the Internet of Things (IoT) are two of the most exciting and transformative technologies of our time. When combined, they have the potential to revolutionize a wide range of industries, including the energy industry. In this post, we'll provide a high-level overview of blockchain technology and the IoT and how they are used in the context of Srcful.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain technology and the Internet of Things (IoT) are two of the most exciting and transformative technologies of our time. When combined, they have the potential to revolutionize a wide range of industries, including the energy industry. In this post, we'll provide a high-level overview of blockchain technology and the IoT and how they are used in the context of Srcful.</p><p>Let's start with blockchain technology. At its core, a blockchain is a distributed, decentralized ledger that allows for secure and transparent transactions. In the context of energy transactions, blockchain technology can provide a secure and transparent way to transact energy data and rewards. By using blockchain technology, we can create a tamper-proof and immutable record of all transactions, which ensures that data is secure and transparent.</p><p>We have chosen Solana as the blockchain for our Src-token, because it is a high-performance blockchain that can handle a large number of transactions per second, and is highly scalable. Our use of Solana means that our platform can operate at a high speed and can handle the large volume of energy transactions that will be processed.</p><p>IoT refers to a network of interconnected devices that are embedded with sensors, software, and other technologies that enable them to collect and exchange data. In the context of energy transactions, IoT devices can provide a way to monitor, control, and optimize energy resources in real-time.</p><p>At Srcful, we have developed an Energy Gateway that is equipped with a crypto chip, which allows for secure communication with the blockchain. The Energy Gateway is also compatible with Helium (LoRaWAN), which enables us to use Helium for verification and some data transfer. This means that we can provide a digital identity to distributed energy resources (DERs) like solar panels and batteries, which enables them to transact and prove their energy data on the blockchain.</p><p>The benefits of using blockchain and the IoT for energy transactions and data management are clear. They provide a secure, transparent, and efficient way to manage energy resources and rewards. By using these technologies, we can create a more decentralized and sustainable grid that empowers home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.</p><p>In summary, blockchain technology and the IoT are two powerful technologies that can revolutionize the energy industry. At Srcful, we're leveraging these technologies to create a platform that enables home owners to participate in the energy market and monetize their contributions. By using Solana as the blockchain for our Src-token, and our Energy Gateway with Helium for verification and data transfer, we're creating a secure and transparent platform that will transform the energy industry.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Energy]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/future-of-energy</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/future-of-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[How Blockchain and IoT Can Create a More Sustainable Energy System]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="how-blockchain-and-iot-can-create-a-more-sustainable-energy-system">How Blockchain and IoT Can Create a More Sustainable Energy System<a href="#how-blockchain-and-iot-can-create-a-more-sustainable-energy-system" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to How Blockchain and IoT Can Create a More Sustainable Energy System" title="Direct link to How Blockchain and IoT Can Create a More Sustainable Energy System">​</a></h2><p>The energy industry is undergoing a significant transformation, and the need for a more decentralized and sustainable grid has never been greater. As a CFO and business developer, I believe that blockchain technology and the Internet of Things (IoT) can play a key role in addressing these challenges.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="the-shift-towards-distributed-energy-resources">The Shift Towards Distributed Energy Resources<a href="#the-shift-towards-distributed-energy-resources" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to The Shift Towards Distributed Energy Resources" title="Direct link to The Shift Towards Distributed Energy Resources">​</a></h2><p>One of the biggest trends in the energy industry today is the shift towards distributed energy resources (DERs) like solar panels and batteries. This trend is being driven by advances in technology, changing consumer preferences, and the need to reduce carbon emissions. As more and more homes and businesses adopt DERs, the traditional centralized grid system is becoming less relevant.</p><p>Managing Supply and Demand in a Dynamic Energy System
However, the shift towards DERs presents its own set of challenges. One of the biggest challenges is the need to manage and balance supply and demand in a more decentralized and dynamic system. This requires new technologies and approaches that can facilitate real-time monitoring, control, and optimization of energy resources.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="the-solution-blockchain-and-iot">The Solution: Blockchain and IoT<a href="#the-solution-blockchain-and-iot" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to The Solution: Blockchain and IoT" title="Direct link to The Solution: Blockchain and IoT">​</a></h2><p>At Srcful, we believe that by leveraging blockchain technology and IoT, we can create a more decentralized and sustainable grid that empowers home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards. By building and connecting their own solar panels or batteries, home owners can contribute to the energy market and monetize their contributions. This is a game-changer for the energy industry, as it enables micro-producers to participate in previously closed ecosystems and helps to accelerate the adoption of renewable energy.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="creating-a-secure-and-transparent-system">Creating a Secure and Transparent System<a href="#creating-a-secure-and-transparent-system" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Creating a Secure and Transparent System" title="Direct link to Creating a Secure and Transparent System">​</a></h2><p>By using blockchain technology, we can create a secure and transparent system for transacting energy data and rewards. By providing a digital identity to DERs through IoT devices like our Energy Gateway, they can transact and prove their energy data on the blockchain.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="the-future-of-energy-is-distributed">The Future of Energy is Distributed<a href="#the-future-of-energy-is-distributed" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to The Future of Energy is Distributed" title="Direct link to The Future of Energy is Distributed">​</a></h2><p>In summary, the energy industry is at a crossroads. The traditional centralized grid system is under pressure as the world shifts towards more distributed and sustainable sources of energy. At the same time, the demand for energy is growing, and the need for a more resilient and flexible grid is becoming increasingly urgent. As CFO and business developer, we're uniquely positioned to address these challenges thanks to our use of blockchain technology and IoT. We believe that by empowering home owners to participate in the energy market, we can create a more resilient, sustainable, and equitable energy system for all.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to Srcful]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/welcome-to-srcful</link>
            <guid>https://docs.srcful.io/blog/welcome-to-srcful</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Are you ready to be part of the future of energy? Welcome to Srcful – the virtual power plant that is changing the game using blockchain technology and the Internet of Things (IoT). Our vision is to create a decentralized community that empowers home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you ready to be part of the future of energy? Welcome to Srcful – the virtual power plant that is changing the game using blockchain technology and the Internet of Things (IoT). Our vision is to create a decentralized community that empowers home owners to participate in the energy market and earn crypto rewards.</p><p>We were inspired by our experience working with Helium gateways and IoT, and we realized that we could leverage the power of crypto incentives to accelerate the renewable energy market. And that's exactly what we're doing.</p><p>With Srcful, you can be part of the solution. By building and connecting your own solar panels or batteries using our Energy Gateway, you can earn tokens and monetize your contributions. This is the first platform of its kind that enables home owners to participate in the energy market in a meaningful way.</p><p>Our team is made up of senior developers, crypto enthusiasts, researchers, and IoT experts, with deep expertise in the energy sector. We're passionate about making a difference and creating a more sustainable future. And we're excited to launch our platform in Sweden, our first market, with plans to take over the world.</p><p>The energy market is changing, and you don't want to be left behind. With Srcful, you can make a real impact while earning crypto rewards. You can participate in previously closed ecosystems and monetize your contributions through services like ancillary services. And you can do all of this with confidence, knowing that your data is secure and transparent thanks to our use of blockchain technology.</p><p>So don't wait any longer. Join the Srcful community today and be part of the energy revolution. Together, we can make a real difference and create a better future for ourselves and for generations to come.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>